

\bigvee

sarmadafzal95@gmail.com



03334545889



Lahore, Pakistan



linkedin.com/in/sarmad-malik-852a7481

SKILLS

React Native

Javascript

HTML

CSS

React



React Redux

ODOO

Github

SDLC

LANGUAGES

English

Professional Working Proficiency

Urdi

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Machine Learning

Artificial Intelligence

Sarmad Afzal

Software Developer

Focused and quick-learning Software Engineer with 1 year of experience in Software Industry. Extensive knowledge of software development life cycle as well as proficiency in several programming languages. I'm looking for a role that uses my skills and develops them further. I'm flexible about hours and can work shifts.

Lahore, Pakistan 3.0/4.0

Lahore, Pakistan

Lahore, Pakistan

EDUCATION

Masters in Computer Science(MCS) Superior University

11/2018 - 11/2020

Project

Worked on a Web Based Online Car Sharing System as a Final Year Project with the help of Bootstrap for front-end design and PHP for backend programming.

WORK EXPERIENCE

React Native Developer Madloops Inc.

10/2021 - Present Madloops is a product based software company.

Achievement

 After successfully completing my probation period I had start working on a Fitness App named as Truvy Fit. I have worked on workout section in this application

Intern

Future Programming Pvt ltd

06/2021 - 09/2021

Future Programming is a Product Based software company which is working on an Online Graphic Designing Platform.

Achievements

- Develop and refine Frontend skills
- Teamwork skills

ORGANIZATIONS

Madloops Inc. (10/2021 - Present)

React Native Developer

REFERENCES

Reference available upon request.